Office of Publications Records UA012
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Subject Files, 1930 -- 2008; UA012.004; 9.9 Linear Feet; 6 Digital Object(s)
  - Africana Center at Capen, 1990; UA012.004.020.00003 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of students/faculty at Africana Center. Date is approximate
  - Alumni Events, 1990; UA012.004.020.00004 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of obsticle course. Date is approximate
  - Alumni Events misc., 1970 -- 1993; UA012.004.020.00005 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of parades, speeches, cocktails, Bealzabubs (?) and train. Date is approximate
  - Alumni Weekend, 1985; UA012.004.020.00006 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of Nell Tracy and Aaron acolver, Andy Simon and Stacy Creem, Kate Schaefer and Fred Ankarcrona. Date is approximate
  - Alumni Weekend, 1994; UA012.004.020.00007 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of 1994 Alumni weekend
  - Alumni Weekend, 1994; UA012.004.020.00008 (Box 20)
  - Alumns, 1994; UA012.004.020.00009 (Box 20)
  - Alumns/Commence, 1995; UA012.004.020.00010 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of commencement, graduation, faculty in robes and hoods. Date is approximate
  - [Art Negatives], 1930 -- 1960; UA012.004.020.00011 (Box 20)
    This folder contains negatives of male portraits, north Africa. Date is approximate
  - Art Slides, UA012.004.020.00012 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of art pieces/drawings.
  - Art Slides, UA012.004.020.00013 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of art pieces/drawings from T-NEMC Ed. Media Center.
  - Asian American Peer Leaders 1998, UA012.004.020.00014 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of Asian American Peer leaders conference
  - Athletics, 1980; UA012.004.020.00015 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of tennis, fieldhockey, equestrian team, rally signs, womens track
  - Barnum Christmas Party (Betty Weiant), 1954; UA012.004.020.00016 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of scenes from the Barnum Christmas party
  - Barnum Christmas Party (Betty Weiant), 1954; UA012.004.020.00017 (Box 20)
  - Biology, 1980; UA012.004.020.00018 (Box 20)
    This folder contains negatives of biology labs, animals, farm. Date is approximate
  - Biology, 1980; UA012.004.020.00019 (Box 20)
    This folder contains negatives of biology labs, beach, plant. Date is approximate
  - Biology, 1980; UA012.004.020.00020 (Box 20)
    This folder contains negatives of excavation, organism. Date is approximate
  - Campus Life (Betty Weiant), 1955; UA012.004.020.00021 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of lounging students, performances, outdoor excusions, Carzo Cage. Date is approximate
  - Chemistry, 1994; UA012.004.020.00022 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of chemistry lab scenes.
  - Chemistry, 1995; UA012.004.020.00023 (Box 20)
    This folder contains negatives of chemistry lab scenes, equipment. Date is approximate
  - Chem Labs, 1980; UA012.004.020.00024 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of chemistry lab scenes, equipment. Date is approximate
  - Children, 1980; UA012.004.020.00025 (Box 20)
    This folder contains negatives of children playing/learning, children with pots. Date is approximate
  - Children and Geese, 1980; UA012.004.020.00026 (Box 20)
    This folder contains negatives of children playing/learning, large group of children, Boston Commons ducks (Make Way for Ducklings). Date is approximate
  - Circus Event, 1980; UA012.004.020.00027 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of circus event: booths, clowns, speakers
  - Commencement, 1990; UA012.004.020.00028 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of commencement: parade, speakers. Date is approximate
  - Commencement, 1965; UA012.004.020.00029 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of commencement. Date is approximate
  - Commencement, 1995; UA012.004.020.00030 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of commencement: hanging robes, professors and speakers. Date is approximate
  - Commencement (Betty Weiant), 1952; UA012.004.020.00031 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of commencement scenes
  - Commencement, 1958; UA012.004.020.00032 (Box 20)
  - Commencement, 1967; UA012.004.020.00033 (Box 20)
  - Commencement, 1967; UA012.004.020.00034 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of commencement scenes, interior Goddard, West Hall, Eaton (nighttime), Powder house rotary
  - Commencement, 1967; UA012.004.020.00035 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of commencement scenes, President and wife
  - Commencement, 1967; UA012.004.020.00036 (Box 20)
  - Commencement, 1967; UA012.004.020.00037 (Box 20)
  - Commencement, 1980; UA012.004.020.00038 (Box 20)
  - Commencement, 1980; UA012.004.020.00039 (Box 20)
  - Commencement, 1980; UA012.004.020.00040 (Box 20)
  - Commencement, 1980; UA012.004.020.00041 (Box 20)
  - Commencement, 1980; UA012.004.020.00042 (Box 20)
  - Commencement, 1980; UA012.004.020.00043 (Box 20)
  - Commencement, 1983; UA012.004.020.00044 (Box 20)
  - Commencement, 1983; UA012.004.020.00045 (Box 20)
  - Commencement, 1984; UA012.004.020.00046 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of commencement scenes and alumni
  - Commencement, 1984; UA012.004.020.00047 (Box 20)
  - Commencement, 1984; UA012.004.020.00048 (Box 20)
  - Commencement, 1984; UA012.004.020.00049 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of commencement scenes, man playing saxaphone, students in Fletcher, signage
  - Commencement BHA, 1985; UA012.004.020.00050 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of commencement scenes, cheerleaders with almuni, signage
  - Commencement BHA, 1985; UA012.004.020.00051 (Box 20)
    This folder contains slides of commencement scenes, cheerleaders with almuni
  - Commencement, 1986; UA012.004.020.00052 (Box 20)
  - Commencement, 1987; UA012.004.021.00001 (Box 21)
  - Commencement, 1987; UA012.004.021.00002 (Box 21)
  - Commencement, 1987; UA012.004.021.00003 (Box 21)
  - Commencement, 1987; UA012.004.021.00004 (Box 21)
  - Commencement, 1987; UA012.004.021.00005 (Box 21)
  - Commencement, 1987; UA012.004.021.00006 (Box 21)
  - Commencement, 1987; UA012.004.021.00007 (Box 21)
  - Commencement, 1987; UA012.004.021.00008 (Box 21)
  - Commencement, 1987; UA012.004.021.00009 (Box 21)
  - Commencement, four prints, 1989; UA012.004.021.00010 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of commencement reception
  - Commencement, Morelli, 1989; UA012.004.021.00011 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of commencement reception, hanging robes, general commencement scenes, S. Hawking
  - Commencement, 1992; UA012.004.021.00012 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of commencement reception, general commencement scenes
  - Commencement, 1995; UA012.004.021.00013 (Box 21)
  - Commencement, 1995; UA012.004.021.00014 (Box 21)
  - Commencement/Alums, 1995; UA012.004.021.00015 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of commencement scenes, parades, pep band, alums, yardwork, children
  - Commencement DiBaggio, 1995; UA012.004.021.00016 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of commencement scenes: DiBaggio. Date is approximate
  - Commencement DiBaggio, 1995; UA012.004.021.00017 (Box 21)
  - Commencement (misc)., 1980 -- 1995; UA012.004.021.00018 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of commencement scenes. Date is approximate
  - Commencement (misc)., 1980; UA012.004.021.00019 (Box 21)
  - Commencement (misc)., 1980; UA012.004.021.00020 (Box 21)
  - Community Health and Library, 1985 -- 1986; UA012.004.021.00021 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of doctor and patient, cardiovascular testing
  - Comparative Anthropology, 1990; UA012.004.021.00022 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of scientists constructing skeleton. Date is approximate
  - Dedication of MacPhie Hall (Betty Neiant), 1950 -- 1970; UA012.004.021.00023 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of parade/floats, Air Force Faculty, military gathering in Carzon Cage, commencement, students on grass, dedication of MacPhie Hall. Date is approximate
  - Dental, 1931; UA012.004.021.00024 (Box 21)
    This folder contains negatives of Dental school, proceedures
  - Dental School, 1987; UA012.004.021.00025 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of doctor and patient (with braces)
  - Dental School, 1987; UA012.004.021.00026 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of doctor and patient (with braces), chemistry lab
  - Dental School, 1987; UA012.004.021.00027 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of doctors and patient (with braces)
  - Dining, 1985; UA012.004.021.00028 (Box 21)
    This folder contains negatives dining hall, student with lobster, cart with food preparers. Date is approximate
  - Dining/Eating, 1985 -- 1995; UA012.004.021.00029 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of dining halls, food fair. Date is approximate
  - Electro, 1986 -- 1989; UA012.004.021.00030 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of class room scenes, electro-optics equipment
  - Engineering, 1987 -- 1994; UA012.004.021.00031 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of class room/lab scenes, lecturers, chemistry labs, computer animation, construction
  - Engineering, 1987 -- 1994; UA012.004.021.00032 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of class room/lab scenes, technology, chemistry labs
  - Engineering, 1987 -- 1994; UA012.004.021.00033 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of class room/lab scenes, technology, office hours, computer lab
  - English class, 1985; UA012.004.021.00034 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of class room scenes. Date is approximate
  - Fares, 1995; UA012.004.021.00035 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of scanned paintings. Date is approximate
  - Fares Certificate, 1995; UA012.004.021.00036 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of the Fares certificate. Date is approximate
  - Final Exams, 1970 -- 1985; UA012.004.021.00037 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of the professor and student discussing, lectures/classrooms, exams, professors. Date is approximate
  - Football, 1970; UA012.004.021.00038 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of the football games. Date is approximate
  - Football (Harvard-Tufts), 1956; UA012.004.021.00039 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of marching band and crowd at Harvard Colosseum
  - greenhouse, 1995; UA012.004.021.00040 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of students/professors in greenhouse
  - Ground breaking Alumnae Hall (Betty Weiant), 1953; UA012.004.021.00041 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of Alumnae Hall ground breaking, auction/musical event
  - Ground ROTC building (Betty Weiant), 1953; UA012.004.021.00042 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of ROTC building ground breaking
  - Homecoming, 1950 -- 1980; UA012.004.021.00043 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of woman and man holding homecoming flag, homecoming flag, Jumbo. Date is approximate
  - Homecoming 1953 (Betty Weiant), UA012.004.021.00044 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of homecoming football game, color guard, crowd
  - Hurricane Carol (Betty Weiant), 1954; UA012.004.021.00045 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of parade, birthday cake and man, destruction/clean up of hurricane Carol
  - Labs, 1990; UA012.004.021.00046 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of labratory scenes (students, squid dissection). Date is approximate
  - Labs, 1990; UA012.004.021.00047 (Box 21)
  - Language Lab, 1990; UA012.004.021.00048 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of the language lab. Date is approximate
  - Lambert-Kingsley Picnic/Commencement (Betty Weiant), 1952; UA012.004.021.00049 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of the Lambert-Kingsley picnic and commencement
  - Latino center, 1995; UA012.004.021.00050 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of gathering outside the Latino center. Date is approximate
  - Liberal arts, 1987; UA012.004.021.00051 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of students at liberal arts library computers
  - Liberal arts, 1987; UA012.004.021.00052 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of students at liberal arts library, books on tables, class room (professor teaching)
  - Library - Seth, 1989; UA012.004.021.00053 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of woman studying, woman with microfilm, two men discussing, man and woman at computer
  - Library - Seth, 1989; UA012.004.021.00054 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of man studying, male receptionist with woman in background
  - Library - Resnick, 1987 -- 1988; UA012.004.021.00055 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of woman studying, man and woman at computer, man and woman discussing, tables with books
  - Library - Seth, 1988; UA012.004.021.00056 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of man and woman at microfilm station, students studying
  - Library Computer Lab, 1990; UA012.004.021.00057 (Box 21)
    This folder contains slides of library computer lab. Date is approximate
  - Mayoralty (Betty Weiant), 1952; UA012.004.022.00001 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of parade/floats
  - Maynally (Spencer J. Brody Laconia NH), 1956; UA012.004.022.00002 (Box 22)
  - Mayoralty (Spencer J. Bordy Laconia NH), 1956; UA012.004.022.00003 (Box 22)
  - Mayoralty 1957, UA012.004.022.00004 (Box 22)
  - Medical, 1986 -- 1987; UA012.004.022.00005 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of eye examination (red and normal), men in labratory, doctor with wheel chair patient, medical students and professors, woman in scrubs, doctors discussing
  - Medical, 1995; UA012.004.022.00006 (Box 22)
    This folder contains negatives of Baystate medical center, pediatrician and patient, woman walking on treadmill (slide also). Date is approximate
  - Medical, 1989; UA012.004.022.00007 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of student and professor with technology
  - Medical, 1986 -- 1987; UA012.004.022.00008 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of two doctors in lab, pinch reading
  - Medical, 1986 -- 1987; UA012.004.022.00009 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of doctors in lab, x-ray reading
  - Medical, 1986; UA012.004.022.00010 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of doctor looking in ear of child
  - Medical, 1986; UA012.004.022.00011 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of doctors looking in ear of patient
  - Medical, 1985; UA012.004.022.00012 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of doctors (medical students) discussing
  - Medical, 1985; UA012.004.022.00013 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of dentists (and dental assistant) working on patient
  - Medical, 1986; UA012.004.022.00014 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of medical students and doctors watching aerobic test/experiement
  - Medical, 1973 -- 1985; UA012.004.022.00015 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of radiotherapy, pediatrics, general care, CPR training, student in library, students discussing, doctors discussing
  - Medical class of 1998, 1994 -- 1998; UA012.004.022.00016 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of group photo medical class of 1998, class of 1994 commencement
  - Medical CPR, 1985; UA012.004.022.00017 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of CPR training, students studying
  - Medical Opth., 1986; UA012.004.022.00018 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of eye doctors and patients
  - Medicine and Biotech, 1985; UA012.004.022.00019 (Box 22)
    This folder contains negatives of doctors in scrubs, doctors in lab, men at computers. Date is approximate
  - Music Festival, 1985; UA012.004.022.00020 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of music fetival and yearbook signing. Date is approximate
  - Nutnt. HNRC Bess Dawson, 1986 -- 1992; UA012.004.022.00021 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of students lounging on campus center walls, students on grass, presidents lawn picnic, West hall, library steps, Memorial Steps, river, general campus scenes
  - Orchestra, 1961; UA012.004.022.00022 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of conductor and musicians, Man posing, men discussing
  - Parents Weekend, 1995; UA012.004.022.00023 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of informational booths, sign for Tuftonia's Day. Date is approximate
  - 6113 Planned Giving shots, 1985 -- 1992; UA012.004.022.00024 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of computer lab, general campus scenes, musicians, Chaplains, Hodgdon "lunch ladies", barn, dorm window
  - Rare books -Tisch, Resnick, 1988; UA012.004.022.00025 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of interior and exterior of rare books
  - Rare books -Tisch, 1986 -- 1988; UA012.004.022.00026 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of interior and exterior of rare books, bust, woman browsing
  - Sci-Tech, 1995; UA012.004.022.00027 (Box 22)
    This folder contains negatives of scientists in labs. Date is approximate
  - Sci-Tech, 1995; UA012.004.022.00028 (Box 22)
  - Sci-Tech, 1995; UA012.004.022.00029 (Box 22)
  - Sci-Tech, 1995; UA012.004.022.00030 (Box 22)
  - Sci-Tech, 1995; UA012.004.022.00031 (Box 22)
  - Sci-Tech, 1995; UA012.004.022.00032 (Box 22)
  - Sci-Tech, 1995; UA012.004.022.00033 (Box 22)
  - Sci-Tech and Dental (no masks!), 1995; UA012.004.022.00034 (Box 22)
    This folder contains negatives of scientists in labs and dentist with patient. Date is approximate
  - Singing, 1995; UA012.004.022.00035 (Box 22)
    This folder contains negatives of Tufts men sining, chorus, artist. Date is approximate
  - sports (Golf, Kayak, Football, Fitness), 1985; UA012.004.022.00036 (Box 22)
    This folder contains negatives of golf green, ocean kayaking, football and woman on stationary bike. Date is approximate
  - Telefund, 1985 -- 1990; UA012.004.022.00037 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of students posing with telephones on memorial steps, woman in class discussion. Date is approximate
  - Telefund, 1980 -- 1990; UA012.004.022.00038 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of students posing with telephones on memorial steps, women studying. Date is approximate
  - Tisch Celebration, 1980 -- 1988; UA012.004.022.00039 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of commencement, musicians outside Tisch, people outside Tisch, Tisch bust, outside function, computer lab, classroom, student and librarian at card catalogue.
  - Tuftonia's Day, 1990; UA012.004.022.00040 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of scenes from Tuftonia's Day. Date is approximate
  - Tuftonia's Day, 1990; UA012.004.022.00041 (Box 22)
  - Tuftonia's Day, 1990; UA012.004.022.00042 (Box 22)
  - Tufts Alumni Weekend, 1993; UA012.004.022.00043 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of man and woman running with homecoming banner, musicians in ponchos, speeches next to Jumbo, children playing in hay
  - Tufts Alumni Weekend, 1993; UA012.004.022.00044 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of man and woman running with homecoming banner, parade, speeches next to Jumbo
  - Tufts Alumni Weekend, 1993; UA012.004.022.00045 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of parade/floats/musicians, children playing in hay
  - Tufts Alumni Weekend, 1993; UA012.004.022.00046 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of man and woman with homecoming banner, children playing in hay
  - Tufts Study, 1989; UA012.004.022.00047 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of students outside Ballou, students in bright colors
  - Tufts Study, 1989; UA012.004.022.00048 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of students posing (next to tree and Bowen gate)
  - Tufts Study, 1989; UA012.004.022.00049 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of students posing (on grass, near Bowen gate, on Memorial steps)
  - Undergrad INT'L REL'NS, 1986 -- 1989; UA012.004.022.00050 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of professors teaching class, discussing with students
  - Urban and enviro LAJ, 1985; UA012.004.022.00051 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of class discussion. Date is approximate
  - Urban and enviro LAJ, 1985; UA012.004.022.00052 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of class discussion, students with technology (environmental engineering lab). Date is approximate
  - Vet open house, 1986; UA012.004.022.00053 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of hot air balloon, face painting, tents
  - Wessell Library - technology, 1986 -- 1988; UA012.004.022.00054 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of students around computer, micro film station, students studying, men discussing, professor teaching class, male receptionist with woman in background
  - World Health Day, UA012.004.022.00055 (Box 22)
    This folder contains negatives of aid and food in Indian villages
  - Yacht Club/Oval, 1955; UA012.004.022.00056 (Box 22)
    This folder contains slides of Ellis Oval, Yacht club, ROTC club. Date is approximate
  - Summer school/TUEC digital photos, 1999 -- 2000; UA012.004.024.00001
  - Murrow Still Life, 2008; UA012.004.025.00001; Soares, John
    By photographer John Soares for Tufts Magazine Spring 2008.
- Additional accessions, UA012.001109
  - Tom Kates Web Project slides, 2004; UA012-001 (Box data_value_missing_30f7f2369278b1267b2bea6684d1fadf, Box 1)